{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Lawrie",
    "predicate": "property/birthDate",
    "object": "1969-01-01",
    "human_readable": "Paul Lawrie was born on January 1st, 1969.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.913928210735321,
            "question": "When was Paul Lawrie born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8261139988899231,
            "question": "If today is January 1st, what age would Paul Lawrie be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8122431635856628,
            "question": "Is Paul Lawrie a January baby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7743842005729675,
            "question": "What is Paul Lawrie's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7099978923797607,
            "question": "On which date did Paul Lawrie celebrate his first birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6841312646865845,
            "question": "Is Paul Lawrie older than someone born on December 31st, 1968?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6792410016059875,
            "question": "What is the day of the month that Paul Lawrie was born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6244335770606995,
            "question": "Does January 1st hold any significance for Paul Lawrie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5455358624458313,
            "question": "What is the numerical representation of Paul Lawrie's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4606606364250183,
            "question": "In what year did Paul Lawrie come into the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Lawrie was born on January 1st, 1969.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2209_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the numerical representation of Paul Lawrie's birthdate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2209_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does January 1st hold any significance for Paul Lawrie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2209_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the day of the month that Paul Lawrie was born on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2209_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2209_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Paul Lawrie was born on January 1st, 1969. This is explicitly stated in multiple documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2209/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt and others."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently state that Paul Stewart Lawrie was born on January 1, 1969."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}